Guide to the Leonard S. Marcus Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2015 Acquisition, circa 1850-2015; circa 1975-2015; 110.08; (98 boxes)
  - Writings, circa 1981-2015; 77.5; (68 boxes)
    - Books, circa 1983-2013
      - Funny Business: Conversations with Writers of Comedy, circa 2007-2009
        - Daniel Handler, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 273)
        - Listening Library Lemony Snicket, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 274)
        - Carl Hiaasen, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 275)
        - Hilary McKay, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 276)
        - Dick King-Smith, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 277)
        - Louis Sachar, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 278)
        - Jon Scieszka, circa 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 279)
        - Funny Business color proof, 2008-12-24 (Box 97 (Oversize), Folder 2318)
        - Don't Make Me Laugh galley proof, 2008-08-27 (Box 97 (Oversize), Folder 2317)
      - Golden Legacy: The Story of Golden Books, circa 2006-2017
        - Antin, Charles, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 280)
        - Artists and Writers Guild, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 281)
        - Battaglia, Aurelius, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 282)
        - Awards - Golden, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 283)
        - Bank Street consultant project, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 284)
        - Bank Street books, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 285-286)
        - Big Little Books, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 287)
        - Blair, Mary, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 288)
        - Bronson, Wilfrid, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 289)
        - Brown, Margaret Wise, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 290)
        - Catalogs, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 291-292)
        - Crampton, Gertrude, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 293)
        - Crawford, Mel, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 294)
        - Dell Publishing, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 295)
        - DeWitt, Cornelius, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 296)
        - Disney, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 297-298)
        - Doctor Dan, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 299)
        - Duenwald, Doris, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 300)
        - Duplaix, Georges, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 301)
        - Eiger, Richard, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 302)
        - Elliott, Gertrude, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 303)
        - Encyclopedia and other major projects, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 304)
        - Freund, Rudolf, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 305)
        - Gergely, Tibor, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 306-308)
        - Gottlieb, William P., circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 309)
        - Hurd, Edith Thacher memorial articles, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 310)
        - International interest, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 311)
        - Jones, Elizabeth Orton, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 312)
        - Krauss, Ruth, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 313)
        - Kunhardt, Dorothy, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 314)
        - Leventhal, Albert, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 315)
        - Licensed characters, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 316)
        - Little Golden Records, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 317)
        - Lowe, Samuel E., circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 318)
        - Lowrey, Janette Sebring, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 319)
        - Magazines, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 320)
        - Malvern, Corinne, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 321)
        - Masha (Marie Stern), circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 322)
        - Miller, J. P., circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 323)
        - Moore, Lilian, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 324)
        - Obligado, Lilian, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 325)
        - Ogle, Lucille, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 326)
        - Orleans, Ilo, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 327)
        - Palmer, Helen Geisel, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 328)
        - Père Castor and Paul Faucher, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 329)
        - Pfloog, Jan, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 330)
        - Printing, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 331)
        - Reed, Mary, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 332)
        - Risom, Ole, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 333)
        - Rojankovsky, Feodor, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 334)
        - Scarry, Richard, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 335)
        - Schlein, Miriam, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 336)
        - Seiden, Art, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 337)
        - Shimkin, Leon, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 338)
        - Simon & Schuster, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 339)
        - Suben, Eric, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 340)
        - Tenggren, Gustaf, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 341)
        - Watson, Jane Werner, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 342)
        - Whitman Publishing, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 343)
        - Wilkin, Eloise, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 344-345)
        - Golden Legacy correspondence, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 346)
        - Draft, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 347)
        - Golden Legacy manuscript (copy edited), circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 348)
        - Chapter 1, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 349)
        - Manuscript (copy edited), circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 350)
        - Cover and notes, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 351)
        - Rough draft, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 352)
        - Draft comments, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 353)
        - Draft, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 354-355)
        - Golden Books contacts, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 356)
        - Eric Carle foreword, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 357)
        - Golden Legacy trip, Oregon and California, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 358)
        - Illustrations, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 359-361)
        - Golden Books history, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 362)
        - New Golden research to do and backnotes, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 363)
        - Golden Books history, circa 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 364)
        - New Golden correspondence, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 365)
        - Golden Legacy letters from readers, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 366)
        - Publishers Weekly excerpt of Golden Legacy, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 367)
        - University of Oregon notes, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 368)
        - University of Oregon material, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 369-370)
        - Golden Mini-interviews, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 371)
        - Golden Legacy final revisions, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 372)
        - Correspondence, outline, and permission letters, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 373)
        - Golden Legacy outline, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 374)
        - Golden Legacy mini-interview, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 375)
        - Chapter 1 draft, edited, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 376)
        - Golden quotes, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 377)
        - Golden Legacy publicity and reviews, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 378-379)
        - Eric Carle Museum, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 380)
        - Key Golden documents and articles, circa 2006-2017 (Box 14, Folder 381-383)
        - Williams, Garth, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 384)
        - Wolfson, George, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 385)
        - Woolworth, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 386)
        - Wycoff, Jerome, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 387)
        - Zallinger, Rudolph, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 388)
        - Zim, Herbert S., circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 389)
        - A Family Treasury of Little Golden Books introduction, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 390)
        - Golden Books Margaret Wise Brown new editions, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 391)
        - Golden Treasury of Poetry, circa 2006-2017 (Box 15, Folder 392)
        - Golden Legacy color layout, 2006-10-05 (Box 96 (Oversize), Folder 2314)
      - Goodnight Moon: A 50th Anniversary Retrospective, 1996–1997
        - Goodnight Moon: A 50th Anniversary Retrospective publicity, 1996–1997 (Box 30, Folder 670-671)
        - Goodnight Moon 50th anniversary edition, 1996–1997 (Box 30, Folder 672-674)
      - Lifelines: A Poetry Anthology Patterned on the Stages of Life, circa 1992-1994
        - Lifelines draft and notes, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1304)
        - Lifelines research and notes, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1305)
        - Lifelines photograph research, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1306)
        - Lifelines manuscript, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1307)
        - Lifelines reviews and honors, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1308)
        - Permissions fees, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1309)
        - Lifelines introduction, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1310)
        - Ages of man poetry anthology, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1311)
        - Lifelines correspondence, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1312)
        - Lifelines publicity, circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1313)
        - Lifelines manuscript (copy edited), circa 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1314)
      - Listening for Madeleine: A Portrait of Madeleine L'Engle in Many Voices, circa 2009-2012
        - Madeleine L'Engle research, circa 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 403-404)
        - Listening for Madeleine manuscript, circa 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 405-407)
        - Listening for Madeleine interviews, circa 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 408-411)
        - Listening for Madeleine text, circa 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 412-414)
        - Madeleine L'Engle family and other research materials, circa 2009-2012 (Box 17, Folder 415-418)
        - Listening for Madeleine publicity, 2012 (Box 62, Folder 1670)
      - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon, circa 1980-1999
        - Hollins University, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 419)
        - New Margaret Wise Brown letters from readers, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 420)
        - Kerlan trip, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 421)
        - Songwaves Goodnight Moon recording, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 422)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography, war and children's books, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 423)
        - Margaret Wise Brown CD liner notes, circa 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 424)
        - Awakened by the Moon letters from readers, 1991–1992 (Box 17, Folder 425)
        - Margaret Wise Brown research correspondence, 1984–1992 (Box 17, Folder 426)
        - Margaret Wise Brown music, 1980–1986 (Box 17, Folder 427)
        - Margaret Wise Brown notebooks (notes, thoughts, questions, interview notes), 1980–1986 (Box 18, Folder 432-435)
        - Chapter 1 (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 474)
        - A Wild and Private Place, circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 475)
        - Chapter 2: New York Here and Now, circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 476-477)
        - Chapter 4: Other Houses, Other Worlds (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 478)
        - Chapter 3: New York Here and Now, circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 479)
        - Chapter 2: New York Here and Now (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 480-481)
        - Chapter 5 (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 482)
        - Chapter 3: The Fairy Tale War (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 483)
        - Chapter 4: The Fairy Tale War, circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 484)
        - Chapter 5 (first draft), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 485)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 486)
        - Chapter 7 (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 487)
        - Chapter 6 (working), circa 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 488-489)
        - Chapter 3 new research material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 490)
        - Chapter 4 new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 491)
        - Chapter 5 new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 492)
        - Chapter 5 final, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 493)
        - Chapter 6 new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 494)
        - Chapter 7 first draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 495)
        - Chapter 7 new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 496)
        - Chapter 8 new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 497-498)
        - Epilogue new revision material, circa 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 499)
        - Retyped originals, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 500)
        - Margaret Wise Brown transcription copy, circa 1980-1999 (Box 20, Folder 501-502)
        - Biography post-permissions, materials returned, circa 1980-1999 (Box 20, Folder 503)
        - Margaret Wise Brown correspondence photocopies, circa 1980-1999 (Box 20, Folder 504-505)
        - Margaret Wise Brown research photocopies, circa 1980-1999 (Box 21, Folder 506-509)
        - Margaret Wise Brown unpublished manuscripts, circa 1980-1999 (Box 21, Folder 510-512)
        - John Mason Brown papers, Houghton Library, Harvard University, circa 1980-1999 (Box 21, Folder 513-516)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography draft with notes, circa 1980-1999 (Box 22, Folder 517-520)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography draft, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 521-523)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography draft, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 524)
        - Margaret Wise Brown research, circa 1980-1999 (Box 22, Folder 525-527)
        - Chapters 1 and 2 first draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 528)
        - Chapter 3 first draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 529)
        - Chapter 3 final draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 530)
        - Chapter 4 first draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 531)
        - Chapter 4 final draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 532)
        - Chapter 5 first draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 533)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 534)
        - Chapter 7, circa 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 535)
        - Margaret Wise Brown and Gertrude Stein excerpt, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 536)
        - Chapter 11 draft, circa 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 537)
        - Research and notes, circa 1985 (Box 23, Folder 538)
        - Harriet F. Pilpel material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 539)
        - Material from Authors League files, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 540)
        - Research and notes, circa 1991 (Box 23, Folder 541)
        - Replacement pages, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 542)
        - Fragments and miscellaneous sentences, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 543-544)
        - Hollins College material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 545)
        - Max Perkins and Michael Strange correspondence, Princeton University Library, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 546)
        - Margaret Wise Brown autobiographical writings, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 547)
        - Margaret Wise Brown papers and related materials, Hollins College, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 548)
        - Hollins Hearsey letters, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 549)
        - Sexuality research material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 550)
        - Typed transcriptions of letters, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 551)
        - Notes from Notes for a Biography by Esphyr Slobodlkina, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 552)
        - Margaret Wise Brown short stories, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 553)
        - Genealogy material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 554)
        - Milbank and Bank Street research materials, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 555)
        - E. P. Dutton papers, Syracuse University Library, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 556)
        - Doubleday files materials, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 557)
        - Biography presentation, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 558)
        - Early research and notes, "What the Wind Said: The Life and Works of Margaret Wise Brown", circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 559)
        - Material left by Roberta Rauch, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 560)
        - Assorted draft pages, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 561)
        - Margaret Wise Brown unpublished manuscripts, circa 1980-1999 (Box 23, Folder 562-563)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon copy-edited copy, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 564-568)
        - Introduction draft, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 569)
        - Information for notes, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 570)
        - Epigraphs and quotations, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 571)
        - W. R. Scott files, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 572)
        - Margaret Wise Brown Bank Street College student file, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 573)
        - Papers from the Kerlan collection, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 574)
        - Charles G. Shaw papers, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 575)
        - Margaret Wise Brown, Baby Institute radio show, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 576)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography, Horn Book Magazine reviews and references, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 577)
        - Biographies of Margaret Wise Brown's friends and family, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 578)
        - FDR Library material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 579)
        - Chapter 1 new research material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 580)
        - Chapter 2 new revision material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 581)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon publicity leads, circa 1980-1999 (Box 25, Folder 582-584)
        - Awakened by the Moon letters from readers, 1988–1992 (Box 25, Folder 585-586)
        - Awakened by the Moon new publishing correspondence, circa 1980-1999 (Box 25, Folder 587-588)
        - Awakened by the Moon correspondence, 1997–1999 (Box 25, Folder 589-590)
        - Chapter 9: In the Great Green Room, circa 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 591)
        - Chapter 8 (working), circa 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 592-593)
        - Half Lives, circa 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 594-595)
        - Margaret Wise Brown corrected copy, circa 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 596-599)
        - Margaret Wise Brown copy edited, circa 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 600-603)
        - New Margaret Wise Brown material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 607-610)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon reviews, circa 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 611-612)
        - Awakened by the Moon Quill edition publicity, circa 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 644-645)
        - Margaret Wise Brown film interest, circa 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 646)
        - Awakened by the Moon reviews, circa 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 647)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography: Bank Street journal excerpt, circa 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 648)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon draft, edited, circa 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 650-651)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon draft, edited, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 652-653)
        - French translation of Awakened by the Moon, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 654)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon Quill edition, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 656-657)
        - Copyright, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 663)
        - Hyperion Margaret Wise Brown, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 664)
        - Research leads, circa 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 665)
        - Margaret Wise Brown: Awakened by the Moon original outline, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 675)
        - Margaret Wise Brown bibliography, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 676)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography front matter and acknowledgments, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 677)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography leads to be followed up on, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 678)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography bibliographics, books in print, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 679)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography unsorted important research material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 680)
        - Margaret Wise Brown current research material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 681)
        - Margaret Wise Brown biography new interesting research material, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 682-683)
        - Footnotes, acknowledgments, bibliography, dedication, and photo list, circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 684)
        - Retyped corrected pages (after copy-editing), circa 1980-1999 (Box 30, Folder 685)
      - Maurice Sendak: A Celebration of the Artist and His Work, 2013
        - Color layout (fourth pass), 2013-02-21 (Box 93 (Oversize), Folder 2302)
        - Color layout, circa 2013 (Box 93 (Oversize), Folder 2303-2304)
        - Color layout, circa 2013 (Box 93 (Oversize), Folder 2305-2306)
      - Minders of Make-Believe: Idealists, Entrepreneurs, and the Making of American Children's Literature, circa 1972-2007
        - Anne Carroll Moore anniversary celebration, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 686)
        - Caldecott and Newbery Medals, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 687)
        - Houghton history 1990s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 688-691)
        - History book 1980s-1990s chapter, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 692-693)
        - Articles, press releases, etc., circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 694)
        - Children's literature articles, clips, etc., circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 695)
        - Articles of interest, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 696)
        - New 19th century material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 31, Folder 697-700)
        - History chapters 7-9, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 701)
        - History chapters 1-3, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 702)
        - Interesting research material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 703)
        - Children's Book Ambassador, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 704)
        - 2000s new material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 705)
        - Houghton Mifflin history outline, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 706)
        - History book recent trends, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 707)
        - Houghton history 1990s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 708-709)
        - Houghton history 1980s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 710)
        - History 1990s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 711)
        - Thor Power Tools case, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 712)
        - Houghton history 1970s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 713-714)
        - Houghton history 1960s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 715-716)
        - Houghton history 1950s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 717)
        - History book 1940s, circa 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 718-721)
        - History book - correspondence, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 722)
        - Princeton University publishing archives, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 723)
        - Vassar College, Bechtel and White correspondence, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 724)
        - May Massee Collection, Emporia State University, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 725)
        - University of New England papers, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 726-727)
        - Maine Woman Writers Collection, Coatsworth Bechtel Collection, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 728)
        - May Massee and Bertha Miller letters, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 729)
        - Office of Children's Services, New York Public Library, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 730)
        - Margaret Wise Brown papers, New York Public Library, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 731)
        - May Massee issue, The Horn Book Magazine, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 732)
        - Dorothy Haas, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 733)
        - Minders of Make Believe epigraphs and titles, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 734)
        - Katharine S. White Publishers Weekly, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 735)
        - Bechtel and Moore papers, Vassar College, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 736)
        - Eden Ross Lipson panel, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 737)
        - William Wise, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 738)
        - Publishers Weekly article on marketing, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 739)
        - Publishers, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 740-741)
        - Booksellers history, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 742)